<resources>

    <!-- Base application theme. -->
    <style name="AppTheme" parent="Theme.AppCompat.Light.NoActionBar">
        <!-- Customize your theme here. -->
        <item name="colorPrimary">@color/primary</item>
        <item name="colorPrimaryDark">@color/primary_dark</item>
        <item name="colorAccent">@color/accent_color</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">@android:color/black</item>

    </style>

    <string-array name="navigation">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>News</item>
        <item>Events</item>
        <item>Ministries</item>
        <item>T-Groups</item>
        <item>Contact</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="About">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Vision</item>
        <item>Team</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="team">
        <item>Ken Kamau-Senior Pastor(On Sabbatical)</item>
        <item>David Obuki-Senior Pastor Ag</item>
        <item>Peter Mwangi- Associate Pastor Ag</item>
        <item>Emmah Nungari-Pastoral Trainee</item>
        <item>Esther Opiyo-District CoordinationTeam</item>
        <item>Jackson Kamau-District Coordination Team</item>
        <item>Arnold Omondi-Creative Arts</item>
        <item>Yvonne Karongo- Worship and Missions</item>
        <item>Peter Mwanzia-Children’s Ministry</item>
        <item>Beryl Karabilo-Children’s Ministry</item>
        <item>Mirriam Wangeci-Youth Ministry</item>
        <item>Moses Musau-Youth Ministry</item>
        <item>Linda Waweru-HR and Administration</item>
        <item>Grace Makandi-Finance</item>
        <item>Carol Muthoni-Administration</item>
        <item>Mary Minayo-Administration</item>
        <item>Denis Ochieng – Tandaza Celebration Centre</item>
        <item>Monica Minani-Tandaza Celebration Centre</item>
        <item>Paul Juma-Tandaza Celebration Centre</item>
        <item>Sam Kimiti-Tandaza Celebration Centre</item>
        <item>Wacuka Kamau-Tandaza Trust</item>
        <item>John Ndubai-Tandaza Trust</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ministries">
        <item>General</item>
        <item>Youth Ministry</item>
        <item>Children Ministry</item>
        <item>Sarahs Treasure</item>
        <item>Kingsmen</item>
        <item>Marriage Ministry</item>
        <item>BOFU</item>
    </string-array>

    <style name="AppTheme.AppBarOverlay" parent="ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Dark.ActionBar" />

    <style name="AppTheme.PopupOverlay" parent="ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Light" />
    <string-array name="youth_headers">

        <item>Daraja</item>
        <item>TILT (Teenz Influencing Life Today)</item>
        <item>HD (High Definition)</item>
        <item>IGNITION</item>
        <item>Culture Café</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="youth_text">

        <item>This is a year-long R.O.P.E.S (Rights of Passage Experiences) program for those in the final year of primary school.
The curriculum based sessions prepare the participants for transition in to teenage with the help and support of their parents and guardians.
The sessions run on Sunday from 11.00am-12.30pm</item>
        <item>We are about mobilizing and building a community and movement of high-school teenagers who love God passionately and live for Him in way that influences others to follow.
We Grow deeper in our FAITH and connect with meaningful FRIENDS over lots of FUN and FOOD.
Our Service runs from 11.00am- 12.30pm</item>
        <item>This is our Ex-cans program that challenges participants to continually define who they are, their relationship with God, their careers and future.</item>
        <item>Is our College Students Xperience that challenges young people to rev-up their lives in Christ, light up their world, spark their gifts, and equip them to be witnesses in every sphere of society.</item>
        <item>These are our Teens and Young Adults T-Groups.
Our On-Campus T-Group meets on Wednesday 6.00pm-7.30pm.
Our Off- Campus T-Groups meet during the holiday and weekends to cater for boarders.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ministry_header">

        <item>Youth Ministry</item>
        <item>Children Ministry</item>
        <item>Sarahs Treasure</item>
        <item>Kingsmen</item>
        <item>Marriage Ministry</item>
        <item>BOFU</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="minitry_text">
        <item>DARAJA-
This is a year-long R.O.P.E.S (Rights of Passage Experiences) program for those in the final year of primary school.
The curriculum based sessions prepare the participants for transition in to teenage with the help and support of their parents and guardians.
The sessions run on Sunday from 11.00am-12.30pm</item>
        <item>In Genesis 6 -9 we read the great biblical account of the flood; how God saved Noah, his family and all the animals in THE ARK.
“The Lord saw how great the wickedness of the human race had become on the earth, and that every inclination of the thoughts of the human heart was only evil all the time. TheLord regretted that he had made human beings on the earth, and his heart was deeply troubled. So the Lord said, “I will wipe from the face of the earth the human race I have created—and with them the animals, the birds and the creatures that move along the ground—for I regret that I have made them.”  But Noah found favor in the eyes of the Lord.”
This inspired us to be committed in bringing up a godly generation that would be found righteous in the midst of this wicked world.
God commanded Noah to Build an ARK so that he and his family would be safe from the floods that God was to send to destroy the earth. Noah obeyed and built an ARK as God instructed.</item>
        <item>Vision: Transformed Ladies setting Kingdom Standards

Mission: Reviving, Restoring and Releasing Ladies for Kingdom exploits

Theme verse:“ Do not conform to the pattern of this world but be transformed by the renewing of your mind…” Rom 12:2
 </item>
        <item>Vision: Every Man Connected, Every Man Serving and Every Man a Witness

Mission: Building Men for Christ!

Theme Verse:“Be strong, and let us show ourselves courageous for the sake of our people and for the cities of our   God; and may the LORD do what is good in His sight.” -2 Samuel 10:7,12</item>
        <item>This is a ministry for married people…
Our  Activities
Praying
Fun
Eating</item>
        <item>Bofu (a Chinese term that means spreading the good news).
We are a ministry that started in Feb 2014 within K3C. Our mission is to share the gospel, make disciples and plant Chinese churches among the Chinese Diaspora in Kenya. Our ultimate goal is to mobilize the Chinese believers to reach out to the many unreached people  in Africa and beyond.
After two years, Bofu has grown to more than 20 people. A number of coworkers from US and Hong Kong joined us. We now have women, children and basketball ministries. Recently, a missionary couple from China also joined us. We look forward for greater things to happen among the Chinese around Kileleshwa and beyond</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
